hello everyone welcome to the day two of
ET brand Equity CX annual Symposium I'm
Aura Shukla and with me is zenat who's
the VP of customer experience from ICICI
Lombard hi Zen hello Aura thank you for
having me here the first question to you
is uh what according to you are the
major shifts in the customer experience
segment that will drive the future of it
to me it is five things first is AI and
automation hyper personalization Omni
Channel consistency data driven CX and
proactive services so let me just give
you a pinch on what each of it what what
do I mean by each one of them so when I
talk about AI on automation it's
imperative that we manage our costs and
enhance our efficiencies using Ai and
automating the mundane and routine
transactions and leaving the complex
ones to be handled more humanly then
when we talk about hyper
personalizations it's all about tailor
made processes where you want to make
the customer you want your customer to
know that you are aware of the channel
preferences the customer has how he
wants to interact with you what he wants
to talk to you about so tailor made U
processes and tailor made services to
the customer Persona is another thing
third we talking about proactive
services so you need to anticipate needs
rather than just solving problems so
it's all about uh proactive servicing
datadriven CX is you have whole lot of
data about your customers
it's imperative that you know what your
customer is where does he belong to what
does he prefer so analyzing that data
and using it rightly is are the major
shifts that I see going from here
another question to you is what uh you
know how important is customer feedback
you know to have the success of customer
experience process entirely with Brands
so I'll answer this with an example it
is definitely a most powerful tool just
to answer your question but the very
reason that customer is giving you
feedback is because the stickiness is
there people who want to leave even in
your real life and human relations you
know will just silently walk away they
will not get into indulge into an
conversation with you or give you
feedback because they don't want you to
improve the very fact that the customer
is giving feedback it is the biggest
opportunity which no organization should
ignore uh no customer feedback should be
ignored because that's the best
opportunity to enhance your processes
evolve as a customer preferred brand and
make them feel valued that you're
listening to them right so that's what
customer feedback to me is I really like
the you know example that you've just
given and thank you so much for the
amazing insights Zena stay tuned on ET
brand Equity social media handles to
know more about what's happening right
here at the day two of the event thank
you
[Music]